## **FAVOUR CHAPP-JUMBO**

Famagusta, Cyprus | https://favourcj-portfolio.firebaseapp.com/ | favourchappjumb0@gmail.com

# PERSONAL SUMMARY

Focused, always ready to learn and detail-oriented Full Stack Web Developer who delivers consistent and professional work for every assignment. Offers 2+ years in the web development industry and top-notch abilities in react.js, java, PHP and flutter. Seeking remote opportunities to expand my web development skills and contribute to company success. Portfolio: https://favourcj-portfolio.firebaseapp.com/

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Eastern Mediterranean University**

Famagusta, Cyprus.

B.S. in Information Technology

Grade: Honor

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Frontdreams Web Solutions Limited

Famagusta, Cyprus.

Web Developer and digital marketing Intern

07/2021-09/2021

- Built Websites using Word press and Joomla.
- Managed multiple pre-existing websites
- Created creative digital marketing emails.
- Stored data in the backend using CPanel phpmyadmin.
- Improved company's client online reach by 20%
- Expanded company customer base by 15%

School Projects Famagusta, Cyprus.

Software Developer

02/2019- 02/ 2022

- Analyzed and designed web and mobile application prototype using adobe XD, adobe illustrator.
- Implemented UI/UX web and mobile designs.
- Constructed an Inventory management system using react.is.
- Developed a healthcare mobile application using flutter dart.
- Build voting portal using react.js.
- Developed a system that generates QR code for each classroom using the laravel framework and stores each input in a database.
- Built Restaurant website using HTML, css and JavaScript.
- Stored data using MySQL workbench.

## LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

School Projects Famagusta, Cyprus.

Head of Game Developer project

02/2021-02/2022

- Lead a team of 5 on our graduation project.
- Allocated tasks to each team member (including me).
- Listened to each member's contributions and implemented them.
- Designed an ERD diagram that demonstrates how data will be stored.
- Designed and wrote a PHP code that stores the important information about the users in a database.
- Prepared documentation for every implementation done on our Ping-Pong game development.

# **SKILLS**

Technical Skills: React.js, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, C++, NoSQL, Node.Js

**Soft Skills:** Detail-oriented, Team Leadership, Time management, Fast Learner, problem-solving abilities, Communication skills.